digitaldividenetwork.org 2015-05-11

# privacy statment - Digital Divide Network

Privacy Statement

Privacy Policy Overview

This Privacy Policy covers the Digital Network treatment of personal information that is recorded when you submit an article, or request an article via email. Other than the information requested in our online forms, no other information is collected from visitors to our web site.

Our privacy policy does not apply to the practices of other companies advertised, or otherwise listed, on the Digital Network web site, nor does it extend to people that Digital Network does not employ or manage.

Author Anonymity

Digital Network does not provide or guarantee author anonymity. Authors who wish to remain anonymous should either NOT complete the Author Profile in their member accounts OR complete it using a Pen Name.

Although discovering an Author's real identity is difficult if a Pen Name is used in submitting articles, there are several ways for that information to be found if the Author Profile is completed with your real name and identity details.

Information Sharing and Disclosure

Digital Network maintains your email address and other pertinent information in a secure database. Your contact information is never released or sold to any vendor, partner or outside agency. Digital Network, however, reserves the right to contact Digital Network members via email as deemed necessary. Such mailings will always include detailed unsubscribe information, providing members the option of removing themselves from future Digital Network mailings at any time.

Security

Your email address information is stored in a protected directory. Access is restricted to Digital Network staff.

Information Collection

Digital Network collects minimal personal information when you request or submit an article. The only information collected in these instances is your name, email address, IP address and the date of your request or submission.

Information Use

If you are Digital Network Author member, your use of our service constitutes a business relationship wherein we provide a promotion service for your article(s). In exchange, Digital Network reserves the right to use the contact information collected during member registration to deliver notices regarding changes or updates to our service, to provide a free newsletter, to inform you of additions to Digital Network, or to send announcements and carefully screened offers and information on behalf of our partners or advertisers.

You may remove yourself from any or all of our mailings at anytime using the unsubscribe methods provided in those mailings. Any mailing received from our company is clearly identified and includes a valid email address and unsubscribe link which you can use to remove yourself from future mailings. Should you encounter problems in this regard, contact us.

Spam complaints will result in membership termination.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

Digital Network may amend this policy from time to time. If significant changes are made in the way your personal information is used, we will post a prominent announcement on our site notifying you of the change.

Author Articles

More From This Author

For women of color, violence – intimate, institutional, and/or political -- is a routine occurrence that shapes their lives, relationships, and dreams. In the case of young women of color, immigrants, and...

Bridging the Global Digital Divide is a tall order even for giant development agents like the United Nations Development Program's Sustainable Development Networking Program and the World Bank's InfoDev...

Talk of a potential Digital Opportunity Investment Trust (DOIT) has centered, so far, of the political feasibility of creating a fund from spectrum auction revenues. To gain the political will, however, many...

Often students from low-income families do not have enough access to the latest technology. The FIU Weekend Academy was designed to provide students from North Miami high schools with the tools to support...

This past Columbus Day, arts organization launched Tropical America, a free online game that explores 500 years of Latin American history. Conceptualized by Los Angeles high school students and artists, this...

Related Articles

Related Articles

With year-round outdoor living in the South, having patio and pool privacy is important for homeowners who spend a lot of time on their patio, or in the pool and deck area. Privacy screens have a functionality...

Huge amount of content is being generated by organizations everyday and with cloud solutions, enterprise social collaboration as well as mobile access, new ways are being adopted by employees for information...

���If you are a normal person, most probably you are not able to imagine how many people are curious about your privacy. And now I do not speak about individuals or secret services only. ...

� � � � �As mobility technology advances and grows more complex, the possibility of potential data breaches increase exponentially. Which is bad enough in itself. But the...

If you’re one of the many consumers who are actively using the Internet, then there’s a chance that you have already tried shopping online. You have a vast amount of choices, and all of the products are...

Latest Articles

Latest Articles

If you heard a lot of great things about Lake District, but you never had the curiosity to visit it, it’s high time you pack your bags and go see this amazing place. Its crystal clear waters and amazing...

So your best mate is about to get married. Whether you’re planning a stag party or a hen party, you have a pretty good idea of what will make for an evening that none will soon forget. But have you ever...

There are many different opinions people consider when it comes to CPR training online. Some do not see it as helpful as the hands on course, others know it is just the same, but the most important aspect you...

All people dream of being heroes one day, but they do not have the right idea about what they can do. Most people dream of saving the world and taking action the entire world will notice, but thinking at a...

There are certainly many innovative materials on the market and they are used in many industries and have various applications. Carbon fiber Australia is used in situations when a lightweight material is...
